What is that thing?
-We gotta get outta here!
-Wait! It might attack if we move!
-Then what do we do?
-There has to be a way to escape!
-Don't expect me to find it!
-Two of us just died!
Everyone. stay still!
I think moving makes it mad too!
Hey. hey. Joohee! Stay with me!
That was a close one.
We'd all be piles of ash right now
-if it weren't for you. kid.
-Me?
You yelled because
you figured it out. right?
No. sir. It was because I
sensed something dangerous.
Mister Song! Your arm!
If I grit my teeth.
it isn't all that bad.
But could you stop
the bleeding for me?
Normally. I'd ask the party's
healer to patch me up.
Ours spooks easily. though.
That's why she only does bottom rung
raids despite being a B-Rank hunter.
I've raided B-Rank dungeons and lived
to tell the tale a couple of times myself.
Something that insta-kills
has to be an A-Rank.
If not S.
Those three commandments of the
Cartenon Temple aren't there for fun.
"First. thou shalt worship God."
"Second. thou shalt praise God."
"Third. thou shalt prove thy faith."
"Those who do not follow these
laws will not leave alive."
Hold on.
So when it says. "God."
it's talking about that thing?
When the first gate appeared.
it gave rise to a number of
supernatural phenomena.
The likes of which humanity could
only fathom in their wildest dreams.
Those who awakened as hunters are
a prime example of one such wonder.
They used their enhanced
abilities to conquer the beasts
lurking in the dungeons
beyond the gates.
Though their power is static
from the moment it sparks to life.
To call a hunter "courageous"
would be an understatement.
For the terrors they find don't
merely strike fear in their hearts.
But can leave them in utter despair.
-Did you see?
-Oh. that video clip?
Cuttin' it real close. Y'wanna
share what almost made you late?
Yeah. no.
Hm.
Hey. your brother awakened
as a hunter. right. Jinah?
He did. The powers he got only
scored him an E-Rank. though.
so he does tend to come home
with more wounds than treasure.
Looked like a regular
mummy the other day!
But. why randomly ask about that?
No reason.
If I was a hunter.
I'd make E-rank look good.
It's too strong to fight.
Meaning our objective
now is to escape.
-Let's collect ourselves--
-I'm not dying in here!
No. I just landed a
contract with a major guild!
Got too much going for me
to bite it in this crap hole!
If that's true. then don't move!
I can do this!
Speed's my specialty!
I'll get outta here. watch me!
Damn it!
That thing can end us
the second it feels like it.
Yeah. we're basically bugs
waiting to be vaporized.
Then. do you have any idea
why it hasn't zapped us all yet?
No.
So it could kill us. but it's not.
What's weirder is any other
magic beast would attack on sight.
The writing! What'd the first
commandment say again?
What?
Oh. the very first one was...
"Thou shall worship God."
God.
This place has its own rules.
What the heck are you doing?
Testing a theory.
Sit down. or...
You aren't done.
That isn't the look of a man
who's given up yet.
We need to bow our heads
toward the giant statue on the throne!
Will that actually do something?
I think you might have snapped. kid.
-So your theory was right then?
-Yes. sir.
It only attacks if you're
above a certain height.
We have to bow down and "worship
God" like the commandment says.
This is your plan
to get us out of here?
Yes. For now.
Guess it's worth a shot.
A little courtesy?
That's what's gonna save us?
Damn. that's freaky!
Its face. It changed?
It isn't doing anything.
Beom-shik!
Why are you standing?
You see? I'm still okay!
It worked.
So that really was all it took.
-No more lasers?
-Good riddance!
-We made it!
-We can go home!
No. not quite.
I thought this nightmare was over!
C'mon. Jinwoo. what's next?
Does your plan have a second phase?
Well. not really. no.
But if we keep obeying those commandments.
I have a hunch we'll be all right.
Meaning the next step
should be to praise God!
-Praise the giant?
-How exactly?
I might have the answer.
As a dedicated student of ethnology.
I have a few extolments for Gods
tucked away in the back of my mind.
O mighty Lord. Praise be to you
who brings order to the world...
I can't tell if it's working.
Looks like it's slowing
down. so maybe?
Show us the righteous path of truth.
That prayer. Wait.
Thy will be done. O Lord.
for only you know the way.
No! It doesn't apply to this God!
We revere and honor your holy name!
O wondrous ruler. hear my cries!
For it's in your name I--
-Shit!
-Let's move!
Everyone. spread out till
we come up with something.
Take my hand!
No way I'm dying like this.
I've got a family waiting for me.
I think the safest place
is up against the walls.
No. Beom-shik!
Look behind you!
Beom-shik!
Praise God. Praise God.
What is there to
praise about that thing?
It's more demonic than divine.
Whatever I do. I'm not
leaving Joohee by herself.
What's the hint here?
Spear. axe.
It's all a bad dream.
I'll wake up an--
Hammer. sword.
Trumpet.
Trumpet! That's it!
I got it.
Everyone. quick!
Run to the statues
holding musical instruments!
If you say so.
What do you know?
Kid was right again.
Hey. none of the statues with instruments
will attack. so hurry and find one.
Damn it all.
Come on. play your drum!
Come on. please!
Is it just one person per statue?
Stay here. You'll be fine.
What about you?
So close!
Not that one!
No!
Please don't die!
Not yet.
Feel like singing praises myself.
Jinwoo! Are you okay?
Barely. but at least I'm alive.
Oh. my gosh.
What's wrong?
Oh.
Your leg.
Enough already. I mean it.
You'll wear yourself
out if you don't stop.
I'm going to heal you!
So just shut up and let me do it!
I'm sorry. Joohee.
What a bloodbath.
No kidding.
I count your arm as a casualty. too.
But I also count it as
karma since you led us here.
-Nice call. by the way.
-That's awful.
You're the one who said
we should bend the rules...
I did what we all decided on!
And I remember how you voted.
Sangshik is right.
I'm the leader
and I had the final say.
I'm the one to blame for everything.
It's no time to point fingers.
There's one more trial left.
What's happening now?
Earthquake?
The hell is that?
An altar.
You know. like the kind
in ancient mythology.
For offerings to the Gods
they pray to.
Proving our faith
is the last commandment.
I may not be the smartest. but
even I know what move to make.
This God likes blood. so it's fair to
assume that it wants a sacrifice!
Beom-shik had a family.
Bragged about it all day. then
I watched him get cut in half.
He and six others died.
If you really feel responsible for their
deaths. prove it to us and God. leader.
-No. Mister Kim. that's...
-You stay out of this!
All right.
Lower your sword and I'll go.
He shouldn't shoulder all the blame.
We voted as a group
to risk coming here.
So is the ritual beginning?
Hm. Hey. kid. what do you think?
Am I supposed to do
something with this flame?
I'm not sure. but.
maybe a sacrifice isn't the key.
Hey. if you wouldn't mind.
Could you two carry me?
I wanna check something.
Just get me right
next to the altar. okay?
But won't we all die?
Hypothetically. we shouldn't.
Did you solve the last puzzle?
Sorry. not quite.
If we wait here. is anyone
likely to come rescue us?
Today marks the seventh day
this gate's been open.
Those statues will mobilize
again before a rescue team does.
It takes a week for a gate
to open all the way.
And then. the beasts inside
can cross over.
A dungeon break.
The other objective of
raids. besides scavenging.
is to beat the dungeon boss and
shut the gate down before time's up.
So. if the six of us fail.
that thing will be let loose.
-Good afternoon!
-And same to you. Miss Sung.
Always nice to see your face.
Hey. Mom!
It's your favorite daughter.
Only hot gossip I have to spill
is that Song-yi was almost late.
Said it was 'cause of "stuff."
Bet she just slept in.
I've also got a national test update.
You're going to have to get
near the altar. too.
We probably need a flame
to light up for each of us.
If anything happens.
it'll be after that.
Hm.
-The doors opened.
-So can we leave?
That's bait if I ever saw it.
That doesn't sound good.
Look! The statues are closing in!
Do we have a plan?
What in their psycho
God's name do they want?
Why?
Wait. Joohee!
Don't close your eyes!
Or they'll keep coming.
See? Look. just like
that old kid's game.
So. all eyes on the statues!
Wait. don't go!
Talk to us. kid!
Now what's going on?
The doors closed a little.
but I think she made it out!
Why? Okay.
The blue flames have been
slowly dying out one by one.
and the red flames go out
when we leave the circle?
Think.
First we had to worship.
Second. we have to praise.
Then now. we prove our faith.
The open doors are a trap.
Offering false hope
in the wake of terror.
Maybe we prove our faith by
resisting the temptation to run.
Guys. I can't.
I tried. but I can't.
Jeongho. don't!
No!
-Hey! Huh?
-Don't you dare move!
The circle will have blind
spots if we lose our fourth!
It'd be comforting if we had a
little more info to go on. here!
We'll escape. too. if we keep our
eyes on the statues and stay put.
The blue flames are a timer.
When they're gone.
we can walk right out of here.
There's also a chance the
doors will shut completely.
And we'll be trapped
inside this room till we die.
I never expected the weakest
hunter of all mankind to be
the difference
between us living or dying.
But I can honestly say that I've
never been happier to stand corrected.
Oh. uh. thank you.
But that said. I've got
a family that needs me.
So dying in here
just isn't an option.
I want to make it home alive.
I'm way past my limit.
I'm sorry.
You're "sorry?"
Not yet. We have to survive this.
Somehow.
I always pull through
every single time.
You two go while you still can.
Mister Song.
I'll stay behind.
As long as one of us waits in
here the doors should remain open.
You both have so much life left
ahead of you. go and live it.
So. Joohee.
Can you carry him out?
S-Sure!
No. No. no. no. no.
Um. sir? My legs
just gave out on me.
You really did overdo it
healing Jinwoo.
You go. Take Joohee and leave.
What? Did you even
listen to anything I said--
You think I can carry her
with half a leg missing?
We're wasting time! Just go!
That makes me the useless one.
so I'll keep the doors open!
Guess I promised to take
you out to eat. now didn't I?
Use this to buy yourself dinner.
Once I make my grand escape.
I'll come collect the change.
How're you cracking jokes right no--
I apologize. I'd let you have a proper
goodbye. but we really are out of time.
-Please take good care of her.
-I will.
I'm glad my death means they can live.
My one regret. though.
is that I didn't enroll in a
juicier life insurance package.
I'll take at least one of
you goliaths down with me!
Let's see what you've got!
I've always been the weakest.
and I've been mocked
for it at every turn.
But I still try as hard as I can.
So this...
Shit. Shit!
This is bullshit.
Bullshit!
I wanted to be stronger.
I tried. but...
I never could.
I get it! I fought tooth and nail to
earn my keep. and I got this far!
But you were past your limit. huh?
Yeah. we all felt that way.
You were making excuses
for your own selfishness.
That gratitude
was as empty as my wallet.
Leave it to a genuine piece of trash.
to use me and throw
me away for his benefit!
I've got a family too!
I wanted to make it home alive. too!
I'm glad my death
means they can live?
How could you think that.
you stupid hypocrite?
No. I don't want to die.
I wish...
I had another chance.